<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>NYTimes Filtered</title>
    <link>https://rss.nytimes.com/services/xml/rss/nyt/HomePage.xml</link>
    <description>Filtered news feed based on specified categories.</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 20:14:14 UTC</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>How Lee Zeldin Went From Environmental Moderate to Dismantling the E.P.A.</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/03/29/climate/lee-zeldin-epa.html</link>
      <description>He once talked about the need to fight climate change. Now, he embraces Elon Musk, lavishes praise on the president and strives to stand out in a MAGA world.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 09:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Lisa Friedman</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opinion | Actually, A.I. Is Pretty Mid</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/03/29/opinion/ai-tech-innovation.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://static01.nyt.com/images/2025/03/30/opinion/30cottom/29cottom-videoSixteenByNineJumbo1600.jpg&quot; style=&quot;width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;&lt;div&gt;A.I. is just what we need in the post-fact era: less research and more predicting what we want to hear.&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 11:00:21 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>Tressie McMillan Cottom</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>He’s Dead, but He’s Everybody’s Weapon of Choice</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/03/29/magazine/trump-george-orwell-1984.html</link>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://static01.nyt.com/images/2025/04/06/magazine/06mag-orewell/06mag-orewell-videoSixteenByNine3000.jpg&quot; style=&quot;width: 100%;&quot; /&gt;&lt;div&gt;George Orwell is easy to quote, but what would the iconoclastic British socialist really have thought about politics today?&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 09:02:19 GMT</pubDate>
      <author>Matthew Purdy</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>‘A Tiny Bit of Math’ Might Improve Your Heart Health, Study Suggests</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/03/29/health/heart-health-steps-smartwatch.html</link>
      <description>Your average daily heart rate is a useful metric; so is your daily step count. Combining the two might be even better.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2025 13:30:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Matt Richtel</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFK Jr. Turns to a Discredited Vaccine Researcher for Autism Study</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/03/27/health/rfk-jr-autism-vaccines.html</link>
      <description>David Geier has been hired as a senior data analyst at H.H.S. According to several people, he will examine any potential links between vaccines and autism that were debunked long ago.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 01:06:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Christina Jewett, Emily Baumgaertner Nunn and Sheryl Gay Stolberg</author>
      <content:encoded xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">Robert F. Kennedy Jr., the health secretary, at the U.S. Capitol in March. Mr. Kennedy has long held that there is a link between certain vaccines and autism.</content:encoded>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dozens of Engaging Ways to Make Media Literacy Meaningful to Teenagers</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/03/27/learning/media-literacy-teenagers.html</link>
      <description>This collection of interactive exercises uses Times resources to help young people find the news that matters to them, understand how it’s made, connect it to their lives — and make media of their own.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 12:03:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>The Learning Network</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brandon Flynn and Jordan Tannahill’s Cinematic East Village Apartment</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/03/20/t-magazine/brandon-flynn-new-york-apartment.html</link>
      <description>In Brandon Flynn and the writer Jordan Tannahill’s 750-square-foot East Village apartment, a bold palette is filtered through a minimalist lens.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 15:31:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Carly Olson and Angela Hau</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What to Know About Adderall, Ritalin and Other Prescription Stimulants</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/03/27/well/mind/adhd-adderall-ritalin-stimulant-facts.html</link>
      <description>Health Secretary Robert F. Kennedy Jr. has called them poison, but doctors say prescription stimulants like Ritalin and Adderall help millions of people.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 09:02:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Christina Caron</author>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Senate Confirms Bhattacharya and Makary to H.H.S. Posts</title>
      <link>https://www.nytimes.com/2025/03/25/health/trump-nih-fda-bhattacharya.html</link>
      <description>Dr. Jay Bhattacharya will direct the N.I.H., and Dr. Martin A. Makary will lead the F.D.A. Both have reputations as medical contrarians.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 01:41:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Benjamin Mueller</author>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
